One Last Dance is a romance, drama, music film directed by Lisa Niemi.
In the wake of tragedy, a renowed New York dance
company is on the brink of collapse.
After leaving the dance world for good, Travis, Chrissa, and Max are
pulled in to resurrect the dance that shattered their careers.
They have one last chance to save the company, re-connect with the
passion and magic, and prove that miracles really can happen.
Travis MacPhearson, played by Patrick Swayze.
Chrissa Lindh, played by Lisa Niemi.
Max Delano, played by George De La Pena.
Alex McGrath, played by Matthew Walker.
Orest, played by Stefan Wenta.
Jerry, played by Timothy Webber.
One Last Dance is a 2003 American-Canadian romantic drama
film about three dancers in New York City.
The film was directed and written by Lisa Niemi, wife of actor Patrick Swayze.
One Last Dance starred both Swayze and Niemi, who also jointly
produced, alongside George de la Peña in a major role.
It was filmed in Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada.
One Last Dance was choreographed by Patsy Swayze, Niemi's
mother-in-law and the mother of Patrick Swayze.
Niemi, who also wrote the script in addition to directing the film, drew its content
from the real-life experiences and struggles of performing artists.
The tone is emotional.